Contact

081294684656 (Mobile) alvin.austin4@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/wandesay (LinkedIn) wandesay75.github.io/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Photoshop
Script Writing

Languages

Indonesian (Native or Bilingual)
English (Native or Bilingual)
Japanese (Limited Working)

Certifications

PCAP: Programming Essentials in Python Certificate

Alvin Austin

Graphic Designer | Web Developer

Karawang, West Java, Indonesia

Summary

I Currently live in Karawang, Indonesia. I'm 20 years old as Graphic Designer and Web Developer, Codeigniter and Bootstrap are my main tools for building website. I also love art and sometimes making a design for my clients and internal project.

Experience

ReArchivu Media Graphic Designer December 2022 - Present (5 months)

Jakarta Selatan, Jakarta, Indonesia

Working as Graphic Designer and Social Media Manager also i made a some content on ReArchivu youtube channel.

Fiverr

Freelance Graphic Designer February 2020 - Present (3 years 3 months)

Tangerang Selatan, Banten, Indonesia

Works with clients and internal projects, making flyer, ads design and art cover album.

Education

Universitas Bina Sarana Informatika

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology · (September 2021 - December 2024)